Finding aid for the Barbara Aziz broadcasts collection
Bentley Historical Library
- Radio Tahrir and related material, 1989-2014
  - November 21, 2006, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:29); (Haroon Moghul talks about his new book, novel "The Order of Light" and issues of Muslim American identity, Nabila Mango reports on her SF-music group "Aswat" as a community integrating activity. Hosts/Producer: Fatima Ashraf, Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: South Asian Muslim author Haroon Moghul, SF-based community music leader Nabila Mango. Topics: world music, Muslim American, Muslim author, Arab music.)
  - December 6, 2006, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:09); (Khalil Jassem reports on US persecution and govt raids of his Michigan-based charity organization and comment on this by attorney Sherif Akhil. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: SF-based radio host and activist Jess Ghanem, Michigan US Charity leader Khalil Jassem; attorney Sherif Akhil. Topics: Muslim Americans, civil rights, Arab American activism, media, world music.)
  - December 12, 2006, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:05); (Ketane comments on status of Turkmen in Iraq under US occupation, Donia Milli\'s discusses making her film "Uprooted" in Palestine, SF -based activists Addasi and Kayali report on their community work. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: US-Iraqi-Turkmen commentator Orhan Ketane, filmmaker Donia Milli, SF based Addasi and Kayali. Topics: Iraqi Turkmen, Arab American filmmaker, Palestine, community activism, world music.)
  - December 19, 2006, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:48); (Music by Arab children, books and films for young people shared by our Tahrir staff, listener calls. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: holiday special, Tahrir staff Ashraf and Baltaci discuss books and films. Topics: books and films for young people shared by our Tahrir staff.)
  - December 26, 2006, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:46); (Three Arab women poets Kahf, Adnan, and AbuSaba read their work and explore Arab life and heritage in their writing. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: poet professor Mohja Kahf, poet artist Etel Adnan, poet Laila AbuSaba. Topics: Arab American literature, poetry, Lebanon, Palestine, music of Marcel Khalife.)
  - 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:40); (Fatima Ashraf speaks with Pakistani-American artist Shikoh about her work and network of Asian artists especially portrayal of Muslim woman's headscarf, Aziz engages Kalhor in one of many interviews, speaking about his work and collaborations, DH Melhem reads poems and talks. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Iranian virtuoso Kayhan Kalhor, NJ-based media artist Asma Shikoh, NY-based poet DH Melhem. Topics: art, Pakistan, Muslim Americans, Iran, Arab American poetry.)
  - January 2, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:02); (A collection of segments: five musicians interviewed by Aziz over the years, with excerpts of their work. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Shahram Shiva, Kayhan Kalhor, Ilham Madfaii, Simon Shaheen, Farid Makloufi. Topics: music, Iran, Sufi, Iraq, Palestine, Algeria.)
  - February 2007, (Aziz interviews Jazz saxophonist SF-based Hafez Modir, on his jazz and fusion with Iranian traditions)
    - Part 1 of 2, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:25:13); (Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: SF-based musician, saxophonist Hafez Modir. Topics: music, Iran, Hafez Modir.)
    - Part 2 of 2, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:29:01); (Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: SF-based musician Hafez Modir. Topics: music, Iran, Hafez Modir.)
  - February 13, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:47:16); (California based Palestinian Abu Gazale talks about his political ambitions and run for congress, Asma Sayeed on using Malcolm X in teaching school history; Al-Hibri talks about Malcolm X and explains work and aims of Karamah law leadership organization. Hosts/Producer: Aisha Adawiya. Interviewees/Guests: Special on Malcolm X, Asma Sayeed and Azizah Al-Hibri, SF-based citizen and political candidate Abu Gazale. Topics: US election candidate, Arab American, Malcolm X, spiritual music.)
  - February 20, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:49:57); (Mattawa announces forthcoming RAWI-Arab American Literary conference, Progress Theater (Muslim-American) members on its founding and production at New York's Henry Street Settlement with performance clips, music. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: U. Mich poet and professor Khaled Mattawa, Progress Theater members Crystal Chanell Trescott and Aron Goodson, Maisha McQueen. Topics: Arab American literature, world music, Muslim Americans, racism, theater.)
  - February 27, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:51:07); (Aziz reviews 2 Iranian films, "Color of Paradise" and "A Time For Drunken Horses"; Abdellah and guests talk about the significance of "Jamestown", racial issues and African American history, listener calls. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Hassen Abdellah. Interviewees/Guests: NJ community members Dwain Wright and Wanda Aiken. Topics: Iran, film reviews, Muslim Americans, NewJersey.)
  - March 6, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:45:02); (Mai Faraj reads from Kanafani\'s classic novel, "Men in The Sun," with discussion about Kanifani\'s political philosophy, reviews books, Habeeb Salloum talks about his research on Arab language, starting with Arab contributions both to English and to Spanish. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: translator Mai Faraj, Canada-based Arab author Habeeb Salloum. Topics: Arabic language, Arab literature education, Palestinian writer Ghassan Kanafani, Aziz review books by Arab writers, Habeeb Salloum.)
  - March 13, 2007
    - Part 1 of 2, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:50:32); (Poem of Iraq" by Iraqi professor and poet Bushra Bustani, commentary by Mohammedi; Sokkary comments on Arabic language in Arab culture and colonialist historical obstacles to the language, world music. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Topics: Arab language in Arabic and in translation, teaching Arabic.)
    - Part 2 of 2, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:23:21); (Longer interview with Mohammedi, who reviews characteristic of Arabic with some critical remarks. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Topics: Arab language in Arabic and in translation (first of a series).)
  - March 20, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:50:10); (We play the Arabic instructional tape by Suhair Sokkary, Abdellah reviews Middlebury's Arab language program talks about the nature and aims of their program, Ginan Rauf explains classical and colloquial differences in Arabic. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Middlebury VT Professor and Director of Arabic Language program Mahmoud Abdallah, NJ-Arab literature scholar Ginan Rauf. Topics: Arab language in Arabic and in translation, teaching Arabic, world music.)
  - March 27, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:35); (Clip by Abu Arab in Arabic, Prof. Brustan talks about aims and character of the Arabic language textbooks for \'living language\', Laila Kamalik discusses being a student of Arabic, from Tahrir archive Jayyusi speaks on modern Arabic fiction. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Palestinian poet Abu Arab, U. Texas Professor of Arabic and co-author of "Al-Kitab" series Kristen Brustad; Middlebury Arab language teacher Laila Kamalik, translator Salma K Jayyusi. Topics: Arab language in Arabic and in translation, teaching Arabic, world music.)
  - April 3, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:49); (Iranian-American saxophonist Modirzadeh plays and talks about his jazz and Iranian roots; media translator and critic Ghazi reports on the range of Arab language media, SF-Poet AbuSaba reads poems (in Arabic) and his life. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: SF-based guests--Jazz musician Hafiz Modirzadeh, Link-TV Jalal Ghazi, FS-based poet Elias Abu Saba. Topics: world music, Arab media, media criticism, Arab literature, Iran, Lebanon.)
  - April 24, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:45:07); (Guests review ideals from which they were drawn to law as a profession, and pursuit of civil rights for Muslims, with direct effects of 911 attacks on NY area Muslims and their work for CAIR. Hosts/Producer: Aisha Adawiya. Interviewees/Guests: CAIR NY- civil rights attorneys Alia Latif and Maya Saya Akhbar. Topics: civil rights, Muslim Americans, law, Muslim women, CAIR, world music.)
  - May 1, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:14); (Ghazi offers critical review of TV satellite programs in Arabic with some aired on "Mosaic" on Link TV, Kitane reports on bombing in Tel Affar in North Iraq and threat of destabilization, and threats to Turkmen. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: SF-based journalist Jalal Ghazi, US-based Iraqi Turkmen Orhan Kitane. Topics: Arabic language media, changing journalism in Arab World, Middle East, Iraq, Iraqi Turkmen, occupation of Iraq, world music.)
  - May 29, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:49:31); (Evelyn Shakir, author of "Bint Arab", a collection of short stories, Aziz reviews recent international films. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Boston-based author Evelyn Shakir. Topics: Arab American literature, Lebanon, Iraq, war, films, film reviews.)
  - June 5, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:50:02); (Fady Joudah reads and explains the poetry of Mahmoud Darwish (English and Arabic), El-Sultany discusses teaching US view and bias regarding Arabs in American, author Sylvian Diouf talks about the history of Muslims in the Americas. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: TX-based poet translator Fady Joudah, NY-based author Sylvian Diouf author of "Servants of Allah", U. Michigan Professor of Comparative Literature Evelyn Al-Sultany. Topics: poetry, Mahmoud Darwish, Arab American community, civil rights, media criticism, racism, world music.)
  - June 12, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:30:30); (Aziz interviews Susan AbuHawa, author of "The Scar of David"; musician Hafez Modir on jazz compositions. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Susan AbuHawa, PA-based novelist, SF-Based jazz musician Hafez Modir. Topics: Palestine, Iran, music, Arab American literature.)
  - June 19, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:53:08); (Omar Mohammedi reviews cases against Muslim Americans and rise of discrimination and mistreatment of Muslims in schools etc., interns Malaika and Hanadi talks about her work, Salaita talks about RAWI conf of Arab American writers, poet Kim Jensen about teaching. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: NY Attorney Omar Mohammedi, Author/Virginia Tech Professor of English Literature Steven Salaita; US-based poet Kim Jensen. Topics: civil rights, harassment, racism, Arab American literature, Muslim Americans.)
  - June 26, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:48:23); (Donia Mili interviews "Palestine Blues" filmmaker Sinoket, Aziz interviews poet Marian Haddad on her work. Hosts/Producer: Donia Mili, Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Nida Sinokat, Palestine filmmaker: Marian Haddad, TX-based poet. Topics: Palestine, film, Arab American lit, poetry.)
  - July 3, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:10); (Warren gives testimony of NY police abuse experience, leading Iraqi poet Nazik Malaika who died recently is remembered by Professor Al-Toma with archival clip by Salma K Jayyusi discussing Malaika's significance in Arab Literature. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: Indiana U. Arab Literature Professor Saleh Al-Toma; NY-based attorney Tarif Warren; NJ Ocean Country College professor and literature critic Maysa Hayward. Topics: Arab literature, Nazik Malaika, Muslim American, racism, civil rights, world music.)
  - July 10, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:27); (Ali Koshak summarizes status of Iraqi Turkmen, Kirkuk City and bombing of Imerli town, Moniza Khokhar announces launch of "Elan" magazine for young Muslim American professionals; Layla Al-Maleh discusses English-language Arab Diaspora literature. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: Ali Koshak of Turkmen Institute, NJ-based Asian American editor of "Elan" Moniza Khokhar, Kuwait Arab Literature Prof Layla Al-Maleh. Topics: world music, Iraq, Turkmen, literature, Muslim American, Arab Diaspora writers.)
  - July 31, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:00); (Nasri Malek jokes with us in studio about Arab comedy, KPFA radio hosts Kathouda and Boustani report on their experience in media as radio hosts. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: NY-based comedian Nasri Malek, DC-Based radio hosts Ryme Katkhouda and LA-based Don Bustani. Topics: world music, media, Arab American arts.)
  - August 7, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:59:54); (Nasr Musa (originally Jordanian) took up Khaliji (Gulf) music on the oud and explains difference of Gulf music and that of other Arab areas, documentary from NY-Arab street fair produced by Malaika, Darraj reads and talks about her work. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: Musicians from the Gulf Arab region, CA-based musician Nasr Musa; PA-based author/editor Susan Muaddi Darraj author of "Inheritance of Exile". Topics: world music, Gulf Arab music, Arab American literature.)
  - August 14, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:54:23); (Hands of Henna" testimony by 4 young women produced by Sarah Malaika, Kashavar elaborates on her book "Jasmin and Stars" a critical view of the presentations of Iranian and other Muslim women in schools and books. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: NY Muslim women Regina, Sarah, Khadija, Shmeh henna party; St Louis Wash U Prof of Comparative Literature and author Fatima Kashavar. Topics: world music, Arab American literature, Muslim women, media, Iran, Muslim literature, world music.)
  - August 21, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:48:26); (Nashef\'s film "Detroit Unleaded" describes her short film (see 2013 interview) her past and future plans, Aziz comments on Brooklyn\'s Gibran School scandal around public harassment, listener calls and commentary. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: Detroit-based filmmaker Rolla Nashef. Topics: NYC Arab School, anti-Arab harassment, Arab Americans, film, world music.)
  - September 25, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:53:24); (Antoon reads poems from "Baghdad Blues" and wars and sanctions in Iraq and expressing Arab culture, world music, Khalil Ben Dib reviews his career as a cartoonist and his candidacy for US president. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: NY-based author Prof Sinan Antoon; SF-based cartoonist and radio host Khalil Ben Dib author of "Mission Accomplished". Topics: Arab literature, American literature, comedy, journalism, world music.)
  - November 13, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:54:46); (Burns reviews with Sarah M. aim and some artists in current NY exhibition "Cultural Interpretations", then artists Nuha Al-Saidi and Haifa Bint Khadi discuss their work, Sarah Malaika interviews Nsenga Knight about her multi-media work "As the Veil Turns". Hosts/Producer: Sarah Malaika, Saadia Aslam. Interviewees/Guests: visual artists Nuha Al-Saidi and Haifa Bint Khadi, and curator Milli Burns; NY-multi-media artist Nsenga Knight. Topics: Arab artists, Muslim Americans, Art, world music.)
  - December 4, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:56); (South Asian American author and actor Rajiv Joseph talks about the NY running play, "The Leopard and the Fox" adapted from Tariq Ali\'s 1985 script, Iranian-American actor Ramiz Monsef on his role in the play and his acting career and rapping and music, NY Muslim art therapist Saadia Parvez talks about creative art and mental health; interviews by host Saadia Aslam. Hosts/Producer: Sarah Malaika, Saadia Aslam. Interviewees/Guests: author Rajib Joseph, actor, designer, actor Ramiz Monsef, US art therapist Saadia Parvez. Topics: Muslim Americans, South Asian theater, art, hiphop, world music.)
  - December 11, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:54:55); (Halaby reads and talks about her novel "Once in a Promised Land" and writing, hosts talk about the meaning of Muslim Hajj and read Malcolm X\'s letter on Hajj experience. Hosts/Producer: Sara Malaika, Saadia Aslam. Interviewees/Guests: Arizona-based author Laila Halaby. Topics: Muslim Hajj, world music, spiritual music, Arab American literature.)
  - December 18, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:53:58); (BN Aziz interviews Arab American author Kathryn Abdul Baki about her latest novel "Sands of Zulaika" and her writing, Miriam Ashraf shares her recent Hajj experience and the meaning of the pilgrimage with her sister Fatima. Hosts/Producer: Fatima Ashraf, Saadia Aslam. Interviewees/Guests: author Kathryn Abdul Baki writer of "Sands of Zulaika", Michigan Hajj pilgrim Mariam Ashraf. Topics: world music, spiritual music, Arab American literature, Muslim Americans, Muslim Hajj.)
  - December 25, 2007, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:13); (Abu Jaber talks with BN Aziz about her latest novel "Origins", who reads passages and talks about writing, host Sarah Malaika talk about Christmas for Muslims and plays music. Hosts/Producer: Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: novelist Diana Abu Jaber author of "Origins". Topics: Arab American literature, Islam, Hajj pilgrimage, world music.)
  - 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:32:09); (Gamal al-Ghitani on his novel "Zini Barakat", his work and life, speaking with Raouf, who also translates (Arabic and English). Hosts/Producer: Ginan Rauf. Interviewees/Guests: Gamal al-Ghitani, Cairo-based author, critic and editor. Topics: Arab literature, critic, media.)
  - January 1, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:51); (A selection of music from around the world. Hosts/Producer: Saadia Aslam, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: New Year special of Music from Muslim Artists. Topics: World Muslim Musicians.)
  - January 6, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:50:39); (Poem by Mohja Kahf, Bina Sherif speaks about portraying life of Muslim Americans and using humor at serious political times, listener calls. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: NY-based playwright and performer Bina Sherif. Topics: Muslim Americans, theater, Pakistan, racism in US against Muslims.)
  - January 8, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:54:27); (From our 1992 Tahrir archive, a documentary of Lebanese disappeared or imprisoned by Israel, resistance to occupation, guest Marwan gives opinion on South Lebanon occupation and resistance. Hosts/Producer: Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: voices form Lebanon in 1991-2, US-Arab journalist Marwan. Topics: Lebanon, prisoners in South Lebanon in Kyam detention center, testimonies in Arabic with English over-voice.)
  - January 22, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:44:12); (Ryan reports on week long annual Arab American Comedy festival (5th year), hosts discuss Muharram Muslim New Year and its significance, Ahmed Shoeker announces activities of Israeli Apartheid Week opposing Israeli policies. Hosts/Producer: Saadia Aslam, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: Arab American Comedy Festival member Ryan Shrein, Ahmed Shoeker organizer of Israeli Apartheid Week. Topics: world music, Arab American comedy, Palestine, Israeli occupation, Muslim New Year Muharram .)
  - January 29, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:49:16); (Sally O'Brien interviews Lynne Stewart regarding government case against Stewart and Stewart's defense in court with history of this and associated defendants' case, listener calls regarding candidates for 2008 elections. Hosts/Producer: Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: US civil rights attorney Lynne Stewart. Topics: civil rights, constitutional rights, Lynne Stewart, Muslim Americans, world music.)
  - February 5, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:44:42); (Guests talk about the aim, founding and growth of the organization of Muslim professionals. Hosts/Producer: Saadia Aslam, Fatima Ashraf, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: Chicago-based Arshia Wajid founder of Association of Muslim Health Professionals, NYU student Janice French and organization PR officer, members Ds. Hassan Choktay and Dr. Osma Shef. Topics: Muslim Americans, health care.)
  - March 4, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:45:00); (Qiess, professor and author of a volume on Arab American artists talks about his research, Malaika talks with novelist and journalist Namou reviews founding and work of Iraqi Artist Association and looting of Iraqi art after 2003. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Sarah Malaika, Saadia Aslam. Interviewees/Guests: professor Faik Qiess author of "The Encyclopedia of Arab American Artists", Detroit-based Weam Namou, founder of Iraqi Artist Association, NJ-based art curator Ginan Rauf. Topics: Arab American Art, world music, Iraq, art, Iraqi American artists.)
  - March 11, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:50:57); (Poems by Naomi Shihab Nye with comments by BN Aziz, Halaby reviews history of Israel and the Palestine-Israel conflict today, Aziz talks about her new book, Kamel Elazedine exports on Elan Magazine NY-launch party, Pirana Reddy on new NY Arab and South Asian film festival. Hosts/Producer: Sarah Malaika, Saadia Aslam, Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Palestinian Boston-based activist teacher Laila Hijab, poet Naomi Shihab Nye, Pirana Reddy of Asian American film festival. Topics: Palestine, Arab American poetry, South Asian films, world music.)
  - March 18, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:06); (Aziz interviews Ambassador Bohari on Western Sahara dispute and Shahrawi aspirations; radio producer journalist Baya Rezk in Algeria's desert city of ElOued talks about her work as a radio host, with review of Algeria by Aziz. Hosts/Producer: Sarah Malaika, Saadia Aslam, Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Shahrawi (Western Sahara) Ambassador to UN in Algeria Ahmed Bohari, South Algerian radio producer Baya Rezk. Topics: Shahrawi Western Sahara, North Africa, media, Algerian radio, world music.)
  - March 25, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:49:51); (Attorney Slovinsky reviews immigration case of Qatanani, followed by testimonials of community supporters, Aziz reviews secret evidence against Muslims and ongoing harassment of Sami Al-Arian. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Saadia Aslam, Sarah Malaika. Interviewees/Guests: NJ-based Community leader Imam Qatanani, attorney Claudia Slovinsky, M Al-Filali, Salah Mustafa. Topics: civil rights, Muslim Americans, Sami Al-Arian, world music, harassment of Muslims in USA, secret evidence history.)
  - April 1, 2008, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:54:04); (BN Aziz archive interview with CA-Arab American poet Haas Mroue who recently died, Ahmed and Amatallah discuss work of Muslim Americans and media's role in coming election, Ashraf talks about campaigning work. Hosts/Producer: Sarah Malaika, Saadia Aslam, Fatima Ashraf. Interviewees/Guests: CA-based poet Haas Mroue, Muslim media editors Baraz Ahmed and Shahid Amatallah, producer Fatima Ashraf. Topics: Muslim Americans, media, US election, world music.)